clipwiregames.com 2018-05-06

# Privacy Policy — Clipwire Games

This policy governs the method in which this website and all of Clipwire Games products collects, stores and manages data related to the users of all websites and games. This includes personal, demographic and technical information; including IP addresses and access logs.

 **What we gather**  
When you play the game, you may be asked to grant personal information. This information is collected for the use of this game, and strictly games operated by the operators of this game. When you access this game, logs are stored, including date, time, IP, account status and general browser/system information. This data is strictly gathered to improve the quality of content on this game. When you play this game, we place a cookie on your computer. This is done to store your current session information. This allows the site to generate pages based on your account and browser requests.

 **Information Disclosure**  
This game will never sell, share or publish any direct information about its users without prior permission of that user. Information such as e-mail addresses are strictly for use of this game and games operated by the operators of this game, including but not limited to sending you updates about the operators games and services.

Under certain circumstances, your personal information collected by this game maybe surrendered to a 3rd party. This includes the following:

  * Subpoenas, court orders or to defend this site and/or its operators against legal claims.
  * To investigate/prevent/act upon illegal activities, fraud or any threat to the safety of another person.

Personal information may be compiled, summarized and used for targeting advertisements on this game; however, this information will never be released to 3rd party marketing companies (excluding the situations stated above). For example, we may choose to offer a specific ad to males on this game, but neither the advertiser nor any marketing middlemen organizations will be disclosed the reasoning for publishing such ads to those users.

The operators of this game may transfer information between this site and other sites they operate. In the event that this game ownership changes hands, all collected information will be transferred to the new operators. Users will be notified of this by a posting on the game.

 **Liability of Stolen Information**  
Security is an extremely important issue to this game. We take every effort to ensure data we've collected is secure, and user/personal information is only viewed by authorized eyes on a "need to know" basis. This includes limiting access of such data to only employees of this site who are required view it. However, if data is compromised due to hacking/theft/etc., neither this game nor its operators may be held liable or responsible for the stolen data; in such an event we will make every effort to recover and secure all lost data.

 **Changes to this policy**  
Minor changes to this policy can be made without notice to the users of this game. Users will be notified of major changes to this policy via a posting on the main page of this game. This posting will be clearly visible on the main page for a minimum of seven days.
